Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Geology, PhC.42.Geology; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automatic Lapping Machines for grinding quartz. (18), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F40-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Uwharrie Siderite, Meteorites, 1931. (2n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Uwharrie Siderite, Meteorites, 1931. (2n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Paleontology, Greene Co., NC. (5), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F41-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Emerald Crystal from Hiddenite, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Emerald Crystal from Hiddenite, NC. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Uwharrie Siderite, Meteorites, 1931. (2n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Uwharrie Siderite, Meteorites, 1931. (2n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Emerald Crystal. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Emerald Crystal. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Folded strata, North Cove, 1927. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Folded strata, North Cove, 1927. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Kyanite, Yancey Co., NC, 1931. (6n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F6-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Esso Well Cores, Cape Hatteras, NC, 1946. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Esso Well Cores, Cape Hatteras, NC, 1946. (n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite, Stone Mountain, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F8-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Granite Boulder, Wilkes Co., NC, 1943. (3n), PhC.42.Bx15.Geology.F9-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Great Lake, PhC.42.Greatlake; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F10-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Great Lake -Bird Nest Colonies Birds, Mrs. Bayard Wootten the Photographer May 1911, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinds, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Botany Carteret Pilentery Club House Remains Core Banks Nov 21, 1941, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Goat, Edgar Bryan Place, craven County, NC, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Cypress 1909(?) Mrs. Bayard Wooten, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis and Great lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1911 Great Lake Poacher's camp- Shelter NW Side of Lake HHB- Canoe- overnight shelter, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis and Great lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Long Lake, craven Co, NC c 1904, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis and Great lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis and Great lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis and Great lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress used in Boston Exposition Pictures Booklet, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F11-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Great Lake -Bird Nest Colonies Birds, Mrs. Bayard Wootten the Photographer May 1911, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Osprey Nest June 11, 1939, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake, Cormorants June 14, 1939, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?) HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co Great Lake Nest Colonies May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F12-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake nest Colonies June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - En Famille Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC May 1912 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - En Famille Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC May 1912 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Along Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC Garland Jones May 1913, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co, NC, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F13-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake 1909(?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Slocomb's Creek, Craven Co., NC, 1905. (6), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F14-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1911 Great Lake Poacher's camp- Shelter NW Side of Lake HHB- Canoe- overnight shelter, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909(?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Cypress 1909(?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F1-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Young in Nest Great Lake, Craven Co, NC 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle Scared. Cattle Range Filled NE of camps May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle back of camps May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Great Lake, Cypress, 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Great Lake, Cypress, 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle back of camps May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Alligator Swimming about 30 Yards Away Little Lake craven co, NC HHB About 1900?, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shore Line of Great Like Craven CO, NC HHB 1905?, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Botany Carteret Pilentery Club House Remains Core Banks Nov 21, 1941, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting, Carteret Co, NC May 1912 Habo vd Clubhouse HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - craven co Bird Rookeries 1909 HHb, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910 (?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinders HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910 (?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinders HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910 (?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinders HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Club Boat Dock Onslow Co, NC Aug 1934, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F2-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - In a Cormorant Rookery Great Lake, craven Co, NC, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - In a Juniper Grove Great Lake, craven Co, NC C 1890, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Long Lake, craven Co, NC c 1904, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Shore Line of Great Like Craven CO, NC HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - In the Pocosin Long Lake, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - An Eastern North Carolina Lake (Great Lake, Craven co?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Cypress Tress, Great lake Craven Co, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F3-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birds Lake Ellis Great Lake Craven Co Camp Bryan June 16-18, 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Bed Lake Ellis June 14, 1939, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910(?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinds HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910(?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinds HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910(?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinds HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1910(?) Ducks- Lake Ellis Duck Blinds HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1908 Camp Bryan lake Ellis Dare, Camp Cook Gathers Lilies, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC 1908 Camp Bryan lake Ellis Dare, Camp Cook Gathers Lilies, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Hunting Craven Co, NC Nov 1910 Camp Bryan, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F4-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Cypress 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Great Lake Bird Rookeries 1909 HHB, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven Co Birds Cormorant Colony Great Lake 1909 (?), PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F5-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Foot Log Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle Range Field NE of Camp, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle Range Field NE of Camp, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Goat and Reading Roove (?sp) Edgar Bryan Place, craven County, NC Nov 20, 1912, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co, Great Lake, 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Foot Log Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC May 1906 Cattle back of Camp, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC May 1906 Cattle back of Camp, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Young in Nest Great Lake, Craven Co, NC 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Young in Nest Great Lake, Craven Co, NC 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Young in Nest Great Lake, Craven Co, NC 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Osprey Young in Nest Great Lake, Craven Co, NC 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Camp Bryan, Craven Co, NC Cattle Range Field NE of Camp, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F6-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing Little Lake Craven Co, NC Arthur and Bob Brimley June 11-19, 1910, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Dam- Lake Ellis craven Co, NC May 1906, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Birding Group June 16-18, 1909, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boating on lake Ellis craven Co, NC 1910(?) Arthur and Bob Brimley, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boating on lake Ellis craven Co, NC 1910(?) Arthur and Bob Brimley, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Lake Ellis craven Co, NC 1910(?) Bob Brimley, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Craven co, Great Lake, Nest Colonies, Birds May 1911, PhC.42.Bx16.GreatLake.F7-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946